<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cristiioan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cristiioan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:11:04 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is Selfhosting Worth It</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-03-02-is-selfhosting-worth-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:11:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-03-02-is-selfhosting-worth-it/</guid>
      <description>What is selfhosting? Selfhosting is making your own cloud at home. It is really great since you don&amp;rsquo;t have to pay for storage in google drive and other accounts just to access more functionality. And as a bonus you get all the customization possible, including custom domain.
What about the pricing? The price for selfhosting can be as low as a few bucks a month, but it is going to increase based on the electricity bill and then specs you need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I have analytics on my website?</title>
      <link>/posts/2022-03-01-is-privacy-a-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 06:18:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022-03-01-is-privacy-a-right/</guid>
      <description>In the last few months I began starting to increase my privacy, by limiting what I share with others and what companies can track me. I made a lot of progress, but I still have a lot to learn. This blog post was made as a way to talk about why I decided to add analytics to my website, what I have been using, how much data I collect from you, and how I block ublock from blocking my analytics scripts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me and this blog</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 05:44:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, My name is Cristian and I&amp;rsquo;m a kid from Romania, Europe. I created this blog to share my ideas, experiences and learnings about things that I care about, including:
 System administration Open source software Freedom(Any type of freedom) Privacy Security  This blog is a personal project and I&amp;rsquo;m not affiliated with any company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 19:06:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Links to my different accounts and social networks Github : https://github.com/cristiioan Matrix : https://matrix.to/#/@cristiioan:cristiioan.me Matrix Room : https://matrix.to/#/#cristiioan-public-space:cristiioan.me Liberapay : https://liberapay.com/cristiioan Email : cristiioan@cristiioan.me
Software Hosted by me Searx - https://searx.cristiioan.me Searx is a meta-search engine, which means that it is able to search for web pages, images, videos, and more. It is also privacy-respecting, meaning that it does not collect any personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 18:48:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>This website is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
